安德伍德遭受抨击
加勒特·沃克的证词非常确凿
Garrett Walker's testimony couldn't be more damning.
弗兰西斯·安德伍德是中国资金
Francis Underwood is front and center in a scheme
影响美国选举的阴谋的罪魁祸首
that had Chinese money influencing an American election.
这是一位声名狼藉  怀恨在心的前总统的证词
Testimony from a disgraced and disgruntled former president.
他为什么现在才发声
Why is he just speaking up now?
你是说他们不应该
Well, are you suggesting that they shouldn't...
重视沃克的话吗
take what Walker said seriously? I mean...
如果是真的  为什么沉默了那么久
If it's true, why stay silent so long?
一旦事态升级
Which is a question I'm sure
我相信司法委员会一定会问这个问题
the Judiciary Committee will ask once it's up and going.
据我所知  弹劾状最早会在周末前
My sources say articles of impeachment could be voted on
进行投票表决
as early as the end of the week.
众议院没那么有效率
Now as if the House is that efficient.
沃克总统才是该被审查的人
Look, President Walker is the one who should be scrutinized here.
他见人说人话  见鬼说鬼话
He's talking out of both sides of his mouth.
别忘了
And let's not forget,
他过去还有
he has had some emotional problems
-情绪问题  -安德伍德被考虑
- in the past. - Underwood has disrespected
作为国务卿人选之前
the presidency since before he was thought of
-就藐视总统一职  -你被这宣传攻势蒙蔽了
- for Secretary of State... - You seem blinded by this crusade.
-当时他还是党鞭  -你们  等等
- ...when he was nothing more than the House Whip. - You guys, wait.
如果安德伍德被弹劾  那么
If Underwood is impeached, then...
那只是假设  这很危险
That's a hypothetical. It's dangerous.
没错
Fair. Well...
汤姆  总统被弹劾后
Tom, where would impeachment leave
副总统克莱尔·安德伍德会怎样
Vice President Claire Underwood?
进入总统办公室  当总统
In the Oval, as president.
如果那样的话
What their arrangement would be,
他们会怎么办  就难说了
in that case, is anybody's guess.
赛斯  第一夫妇现在情况如何
Seth, what is this like right now for the first couple?
他们在回避这些纷扰
They're avoiding all of this distraction.
他们在继续为美国人民服务
They're continuing to do the work of the American people.
人人影视倾情奉献
翻译   草草
翻译   肉松
翻译   国士章鱼X
翻译   杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译   苏小黛
翻译   盐湖凉开水
时间轴   壬虚浪影
时间轴   萌
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第五季  第十一集
-党内警告  -不行
- Censure. - No.
我理解马克的意思
I see Mark's point.
根本不可能阻止众议院的共和党人
There is no way to stop the Republicans in the House.
沃克不是可信的证人
Walker's not a reliable witness.
他的证词能被核实吗
Is what he said verifiable?
所以弹劾在所难免
So, impeachment is inevitable.
好吧  那只是假设
Well, that's... that's a presumption.
民主党掌权的参议院
The Democratic Senate
不会愿意弹劾民主党总统
will not be inclined to remove a Democratic president.
但他们需要政治掩护
But they need political cover.
党内警告能满足他们
Censure will help them with that.
他们可能提出其他的惩罚
I mean, they might propose other penalties,
罚款  谴责声明
a fine, a statement of condemnation
但他们不会去证实犯罪行为
but they'll stop short of finding criminal wrongdoing.
但如果进展得快  大家都能继续前进了
And if it happens quickly, everyone can move on.
你俩私下商量过这件事吗
Did you two get together on this privately?
没有
No.
弗兰西斯  这是挽救你第一任期的办法
Francis, this is one way to salvage your first term.
沃克本该保持沉默的
Walker was supposed to plead the Fifth.
事情出现了意外变化
Well, things took an unexpected turn.
对  他违背了协议
Yes. He went back on his deal,
因为他和自己的证词一样不可靠
because he's as pliable as his testimony.
马克  我不会被众议院弹劾
Mark, I will not be impeached in the House
那绝对到不了参议院
and it will never get to the Senate.
我们要让加勒特·沃克名誉扫地
We will destroy Garrett Walker's credibility
这事便会不攻自破
and the case will fall apart.
好吧
Okay.
我能得到豁免权吗
Can I get immunity?
看你能提供什么信息
Depends on what you give them.
我会联系副主席
I'll reach out to a ranking member,
但你无法匿名
but you're not gonna get anonymity...
凯茜
Cathy.
-简  -你好
- Jane. - Hello?
我为你牵肠挂肚  你能相信发生这种事吗
You've been on my mind. Can you believe what's going on?
抱歉失陪一下
Excuse me for a moment.
就像我母亲说的  "简直是一团乱麻"
As my mother used to say, "It's a red hot mess."
弗兰克·安德伍德倒霉不代表你也得遭殃
Frank Underwood's demise doesn't have to be yours.
还有许多非营利性
There are non-profits,
民间组织非常希望和你合作
NGOs that would be dying to work with you.
据我所知  我的工作还没丢
Well, as far as I know, I still have a job.
当然没有
No, of course.
但谁知道他们接下来会去查谁
But who knows who they'll come after next?
我本来就不是核心圈子的人
I was never part of their inner circle.
你找莫琳很聪明  她是个好律师
You were smart to go with Maureen. She's a good lawyer.
要说谁能帮你全身而退  就是她了
If someone can find you an exit, it's her.
我不会就这么轻易退场的
Well, I'm not gonna go away easily,
所以多谢你的关心  简
so thank you for your concern, Jane.
我是关心
It is concern.
你认为副总统
do you think the vice president
知道这些事情吗
had any knowledge of this stuff?
我说了  我真的不知道
Well, as I said, I have no idea.
如果克莱尔挺过这关  成了总统
If... if Claire survives this and becomes president,
那你要怎么办
where does that leave you?
我好歹也打拼了三十多年  简
Well, I've been at this for 30 years, Jane,
我想我还是能挺过去的
so I think I can survive.
亲爱的  我不是想吓唬你
Oh, honey, I didn't mean to alarm you.
我也没害怕
I'm not alarmed.
我只是想说
All I'm trying to say,
我支持你
I'm on your side.
如果是在继续当总统还是下台之间选择的话
If it's the difference in being in office or being out,
我们可以想办法绕过去
we can work around that.
戴着手铐想办法吧
Working in handcuffs.
党内警告是个挫折  但还没有输
Censure is a setback. It's not a loss.
你还真是自信满满  执拗得很啊
You're very confident and very insistent.
我们会撑过去的  弗兰西斯
We can come out of this, Francis.
你是说你自己吧
No, you mean you can.
哪怕就一次  你能不能
Can you, for once,
干脆点  接受开价  别再还价了
just take something at face value instead of fighting it?
就好像我过去造的孽能洗清似的
As if I can be washed clean of past sins.
-你认识我多久了  -很久了
- How long have you known me? - Forever.
那你有多了解我
How well do you know me?
就算你克莱尔·安德伍德
How, in your wildest imagination,
再怎么尽情发动想象力
could you, Claire Underwood,
也不该以为我会接受这个
think I would be okay with this?
求你考虑一下吧
Think about it, please.
这关乎我的总统之位
This is the fate of my presidency!
人民想原谅你
The people want to forgive you.
接受吧
Let them.
快点出来  再给我讲讲
Come out here already. Give me the rest of it.
汉默施密特是个彻头彻尾的工作狂
Hammerschmidt is a straight-up workaholic.
但是他就快查出什么了
But... he's getting close.
线索慢慢拼凑起来了
Putting the pieces together.
他还查得这么起劲做什么
What's he still grinding so hard for?
看来沃克就要扳倒安德伍德了
Looks like Walker's gonna bring Underwood down.
我不想再谈工作了
I don't wanna do this anymore.
佐伊·巴恩斯  瑞秋·波斯纳
Zoe Barnes. Rachel Posner.
肖恩  别说了
Sean, please, I...
是我想把他的调查拉回来
I was the one trying to get him back on that.
-结果害得我被解雇了  -能不说这些了吗
- That's what got me fired. - Can we stop talking about this?
-我的酒呢  -别这样
- Where's my drink? - Don't do that.
看着我  看我
Look at me. Look.
我这就  不说了
This is me... not talking.
过来  过来
Come here. Come here.
如果有我能帮忙的地方  就告诉我
But if I can be of any help, you let me know.
看我不收拾你
You're gonna get it.
让我也喝一口
Give me a taste of that.
慢点
Slow down.
靠边停
Pull over!
你今天骑得很使劲啊  总统先生  还好吗
You're going pretty hard, Mr. President. You okay?
对于一个命运悬而未决的人来说  够好的了
Well enough for a man whose fate is hanging in the balance.
不对
No.
你的命运已经定了
Your fate is sealed.
怎么说
Oh, how's that?
你又"预见"到了什么了吗  艾瑞克
You have a vision for me, Eric?
就算你被弹劾定罪
Even if you're impeached and convicted...
你还是会创造历史
you still make history.
奥古斯都·安德伍德只是又一个
Augustus Underwood was just another redneck
选错了立场的农民罢了
who died fighting for the wrong side,
除了你和我没人记得住他
forgotten by everyone but you and me.
但如果弗兰西斯·安德伍德下台了呢
But if Francis Underwood is removed from office?
你的遗产也不会消散
Your legacy won't die.
反而会更加牢固
It'll be solidified.
你会遗臭万年
You'll be infamous.
政治遗产和遗臭万年可不是一回事
Legacy and infamy are not the same thing.
你将被人铭记  谁在乎原因呢
You'll be remembered. Who cares why?
我得回去了
I have to get back.
等等  听我解释一下
Hold up. Let me explain.
弗兰西斯
Francis.
Francis?
我说清楚
Just to be clear,
我其实一直都知道你在看着我
it's not that I haven't always known you were there.
只是我对你的情感很复杂
It's that I have mixed feelings about you.
我质疑你的意图
I question your intentions...
而且我对关注感到矛盾
and I'm ambivalent about attention.
但别当我是针对你
But don't take it personally.
我对每个人的感觉几乎都是这样的
It's how I feel about most everybody.
我们怎能相信他说的话呢
How can we trust anything he says?
沃克的证词揭露了不止安德伍德的不法行为
加勒特·沃克任总统期间一直在用药
Garrett Walker was medicated while he was in office.
这我们都知道
We all know that.
不  这不是论据  这是事实
No, it's not a talking point. It's the truth.
我们不知道他具体用的什么药
We don't know exactly what he was taking.
私下说
Off the record...
你能告诉我汤姆·汉默施密特在忙什么吗
can you tell me what Tom Hammerschmidt's working on?
拜托  你们俩在那儿就没有交集吗
Come on, you two don't cross paths over there?
他为了一篇报道联系过我
He reached out to me on a story.
之后就没回音了
I never heard back.
好  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
双城记
查尔斯·狄更斯
今天是你的生日
随便你相不相信他说的
You can believe what he's saying or not.
趁牙齿还在
快微笑一个
但加勒特·沃克在服药...
But Garrett Walker was taking serious medication...
千万不要把一个陌生的U盘
Never... never put an unknown flash drive
插在联网的电脑上  千万不要
into a networked computer. Never.
你不用一直说这话
You don't have to keep telling me.
-是我叫你来的  记得吗  -记得
- I called you, remember? - Yeah.
好  看看能糟糕到哪里去
Okay. Do your worst.
好  目前来看都还好
Okay. So far so good.
有东西
There is something.
谢谢
Thank you.
我得挂了
I have to go.
没事吧
Everything okay?
-现在不方便  -今晚见
- Not now. - See you tonight?
等我忙完了给你打回去
I'll call you when I'm done.
我觉得出现了泄密者
I think there's a leak.
安德伍德政府的
In the Underwood Administration.
不知道
No idea.
不  这话说得有点早
Well, no, that's a little premature.
这不是水门事件  现在还不是
This isn't Watergate... yet.
嗯
Yeah.
好
Okay.
艾力克斯
Alex.
司法委员会是不可能了
So... Judiciary won't be happening for you.
只有零星几个民主党人的位置
Just the few slots for Democrats.
都刚被领导层安排了
Leadership just filled those
保守派民主党人  抱歉
with a couple of old Blue Dogs. Sorry.
有一件事你倒是说对了
Well, you were right about one thing.
加勒特的证词没有让我交到朋友
Garrett's testimony did not make me any friends.
在你们党不行
Not in your party, no.
今天早晨  我正式成为无党派议员了
Well, as of this morning, I'm officially an independent.
我觉得共和党能给我在司法委员会找个差事
I think the GOP can find me a place on judiciary.
-好吧  艾力克斯  -这一步很明智
- Okay, Alex. - It's a good move.
四年后
Four years from now,
我觉得选民们会想要一个局外人的
I think an outsider's what the voter will be looking for.
是啊  未来属于第三党候选人
Yeah, third-party candidate is the future,
而且永远都是
and always will be.
加勒特·沃克为什么改主意了
Why did Garrett Walker change his mind?
不是我让他改主意的
It wasn't me who made that happen.
我不知道
I don't know.
有时我们不知为何  但事情就发生了
Sometimes things happen without us knowing why.
他们逮捕了一个他们明知清白的人
They arrested someone they knew was innocent.
-斯坎伦州长否认了  -他当然会了
- Governor Scanlon denies it. - Of course he does.
-而国安局无可奉告  -一贯如此
- And the NSA has no comment. - As a rule.
不行  出去
No, out. Get out.
请五分钟后再来
Five minutes, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
联调局确认他们逮捕了卡拉比
The FBI confirms that they arrested Kalabi
他正在候审  但仅此而已
and that he's awaiting trial, but that's all.
没错  仅此而已
That's right, that's all.
但是有联调局的探员
But there are agents in the FBI
对此案的处理方式很不满
who were not happy with the way this went down.
而且没有一个人允许我们
And not one of them will let us
公开他们的姓名
use their name on the record.
我们无法核实
We can't confirm the story.
汤姆  这么大的事没有消息源是不能发的
Tom, we can't run a story this big without a source.
-我知道  -本报从来没这么做过
- No. I know. I know. - This paper has never done that.
-我知道  -谁知道是什么人给你发的
- I know. - Who knows who sent you this?
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
我需要你帮我放个料出去
I need you to float something out for me.
给头条网
Give it to Slugline.
你要我怎么说
What do you want me to say?
就说你在办公室偶然看到
You picked it up here in the office.
虽然没查实
It's not confirmed...
但似乎值得报道
but it seems like a story.
去印出来吧
Go ahead and print it.
我对你这么做完全不知情
And I had no idea you're doing this.
操  我操  操操操
Fuck! Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
在我看来
Well, it looks to me like
安德伍德团队错误逮捕了一名
the Underwood campaign had a Muslim visiting the US
访美穆斯林  就为了
wrongly arrested in order to
能在大选日影响选情
influence the vote on Election Day.
如果你相信这个
And if you believe that,
那你就不得不质疑
then you have to ask some questions
这对田纳西州选情的影响有多大
about the impact this had on the results in Tennessee,
当时各方均预计安德伍德总统会输掉田州
where President Underwood was predicted to lose.
我们都知道哈里发国的威胁是真实的
We all know that ICO is a real threat.
没人否认这一点  而且我
Nobody is denying that, and I...
今天不要转接电话进来
No calls get through to me, not today.
如果有媒体问你
And if you get pressed,
就说白宫目前没有任何评论
the White House has no comment at this time.
好  先生
Yes, sir.
拜托你人走关门
Close the door behind you, please.
这事你知道多少
What do you know about this?
首先  你这么问什么意思
First of all, what are you getting at?
其次  如果我知情的话
And secondly, if I had any information,
我也肯定不会瞒着不报
I wouldn't be keeping it to myself.
赛斯  我就跟你直说了
Seth, I am asking you straight up.
如果你知道什么  现在就告诉我
If you know anything, you tell me now.
-别等我动手去查  -不然呢
- Don't make me find out. - Or what?
你想怎么办  道格
What are you gonna do, Doug?
拿白宫马克杯闷死我吗
You gonna suffocate me with a White House mug?
局面已经失控了
The shit is hitting the fan
如果我们再不赶快动手
and we're all going to be covered in it
就都会被牵连进去
if we don't get to work.
请问  我可以继续忙了吗
Now... can I please get back to it?
妈的
Shit.
我们只需要启动
We're essentially turning on
一台早已就位的设备
an apparatus that's already in place.
我们会打开音频接收
We'll enable audio capabilities.
所有电话  电邮和短信
All calls, e-mails, messages
进出白宫的一切通讯
in and out of the White House
都会被监控归档
will be monitored and archived.
搜索泄密者期间每通电话都会被录音
Every phone call will be recorded as we search for the leak.
视频监控呢
Video surveillance?
我们可以再加装设备
We can install additional devices,
-可是  -用现成的就行
- but... - We use what's already there.
我们将能够监视监听白宫所有职员的
It enables us to look and listen in on every computer
每一台电脑和手机
and every cell phone of everyone working for us.
我们会成立一个卫星监控办公室
We'll set up a satellite office
成员仅限我本人和斯坦普先生
limited to Mr. Stamper and myself.
格林助理局长和我
Assistant Director Green and I
会汇报任何有价值的情报
will bring whatever is valuable forward.
我想要直接访问权
I want direct access.
实时影像
Live streaming.
我向您保证  总统先生
I assure you, Mr. President,
有什么有用内容我们都会呈递给您
we'll bring you anything of substance.
去吧
Do it.
不用说
And needless to say...
我只向您汇报  先生
I report only to you, sir.
我要知道是谁在坑我
I wanna know who did this to me.
我去查  先生
I'm on it, sir.
你对道格有顾虑吗
You're having doubts about Doug?
-怎么  你有吗  -没有  就是
- Why? Are you? - No, I'm just...
我现在大概质疑一切了
I'm questioning everything, I guess.
这事解决之前
Until this is resolved,
你和我对于我们的言行
you and I should be very careful
要万分小心了
about what we say or do.
我们的私人需求得放到一边
And our personal needs have to be put aside.
你了解一些人  认识他们多年
You know people. You know them for years.
而突然  他们就像出现在你厨房里的陌生人
And then... suddenly they're like strangers in your kitchen.
熟悉和陌生只有一线之隔
Familiar can turn foreign on a dime.
-我能做什么吗  -你可以别妄动
- Is there anything I can do? - You can be quiet.
道格  我可不是泄密者  你知道的
Doug, I am not the leak here. You know that.
-我会再联系  -别挂
- I'll be in touch. - Don't hang up.
要我列出我为本届政府
Do I need to make a list of the risks
冒的风险吗
I've taken for this administration?
都是我从未做过的事
Things I have never done before.
我们当面谈吧  好吗
Let's just talk in person, okay?
谁啊
Yes?
请找莉安·哈维
LeAnn Harvey, please.
-是谁  -联调局
- Who is it? - FBI.
如果你能想到什么
If you think of anything,
名片最下面是我的手机号
that's my cell at the bottom of the card.
是自杀吗
Was it a suicide?
枪管抵着他的眼睛
Barrel of the gun was pressed against his eye, so...
你是他的联系人  他会做出这样的事吗
You were his contact. Would he do something like that?
我觉得不会
I don't think so.
或许他没有
Well, maybe he didn't.
-那枪呢  -问题就在这里
- And the gun? - That's the thing.
不见了
It's not there.
或许是酒店的住客或员工拿走了
Maybe someone staying at the hotel or working there took it.
你们会告知我吧
You'll let me know?
当然
Yeah. Sure.
马克
Mark...
副总统和我商量了
the vice president and I have discussed it and...
我们接受你的立场了
we've come around to your position.
很好
Very good.
鉴于现在爆出的新闻
Uh, considering the news that's breaking,
恐怕不会那么容易了
it's not going to be quite as easy.
知道消息是哪来的吗
Any idea where this story came from?
还不知道  但很快就会知道
No, not yet. But I will soon.
我会告诉他们你愿接受党内警告
I'll let it be known that you're open to censure.
你该知道
And you should be aware.
这并不意外
It's not surprising.
罗梅洛要进入司法委员会了
Romero is moving over to the Judiciary Committee.
他为什么不呢
Well, why wouldn't he?
他想把这事做到底  他还没放过我呢
He wants to see this through. He's still coming after me.
我猜两方的领导层都已经受够他了吧
Well, I imagine leadership from both parties has had enough of him.
嗯  我不想往小了说
Yeah, I don't want to diminish this.
我们在控制损失
We are in damage control.
克莱尔  我觉得
Claire, I think...
或许你最好还是
it might be best for you to
尽量别掺和这事
stay out of this as much as possible.
不  我要维护总统
No, I... I will defend the president.
我觉得最好是
Vice presidential business as usual
副总统一切照旧
is the way to play it, I think.
这事你得相信我的直觉
You need to trust my instincts on this one.
-好  -谢谢  马克
- Okay. - Thank you, Mark.
谢谢
Thank you.
你可能并不总同意他  但你喜欢他
You may not always agree with him, but you like him.
我喜欢他清醒的头脑
I like his clarity.
别忘了  他的候选人输了
Let's just not forget, his candidate lost.
而现在他为你工作
And now he works for you.
不  我觉得他其实在为你工作  不是吗
No, I think he's really working for you, isn't he?
别疑神疑鬼  弗兰西斯
Don't get paranoid, Francis.
现在不  更待何时
If not now, when?
你得走了
You have to go.
什么
I what?
你得离开
You need to leave.
发生什么了
What's happened?
这里就是容不下你了
There's just no place for you here anymore.
你考虑过了吗
Have you been thinking about this?
是的
Yes.
我不同意
I don't agree.
我说得很明白了
I'm completely clear about it.
你可以喝完你的咖啡
You can finish your coffee.
你怎么做到的
How do you do that?
就那样关闭感情
Just... turn off like that?
走吧  汤姆
Please go, Tom.
走
Go.
好吧
Okay.
如果这是你的选择
If that's what you choose.
也来点
Join us?
算了  我不想把新肝也喝坏
No, I'm trying not to wear out the new model.
什么事你们大驾光临
So, to what do I owe this pleasure?
我就直说了  弗兰克
Well, I'll get right to it, Frank.
众议院的共和党人终于有一次
Well, for once, the House Republicans...
能完成工作了
are getting something done.
坏消息是  那就是弹劾你
And the bad news is, is that thing is impeaching you.
我觉得司法委员会
Oh, I think the judiciary
离做出决定还差得远呢
is a long way from making any sort of decision.
我得知  他们接下来几天里就会把
They're sending articles of impeachment to the House
弹劾状送交众议院
in the next few days, I'm told.
而今早的新闻更是火上浇油
And that news this morning is just adding fuel to the fire.
天呐
Jesus Christ.
我是来问你是否...
And I'm here to ask if you...
你是否能考虑辞职
Would you consider resigning
而不是把这事扯到参议院去
instead of dragging this through the Senate?
你们俩疯了吗
Have the two of you lost your minds?
你  泰瑞  你自己也在受调查
And you, Terry, you're under investigation yourself
你还敢跑来跟我说这话
and you dare come here and ask me this?
我经常恨你恨得牙根痒
I've often hated your guts,
但我承认  我会怀念你的
but I have to admit, I'll miss you.
鲍勃  别忘了
Oh, Bob, in case you've forgotten,
参议院是民主党的
the Senate is Democratic.
-我短时间内不会走人的  -不是你
- I won't be leaving anytime soon. - Oh, not you.
是我  我已经干不动了
Me. I'm getting too old for this.
什么
What?
众议院离了鲍勃·博奇不得面目全非了
A House without Bob Birch? It will be unrecognizable.
我觉得已经是这样了  天呐
I feel like it already is. God...
一直都是这么肮脏的吗
Was it always this dirty?
那不可能
That's impossible.
我们的先辈就要更干净些吗
Were the men before us any more moral?
更配得上他们所处的位置
Any more worthy of the power and position
和所拥有的权力吗
that they had found themselves in?
更有能力为公众牟利吗
Any more capable of doing a single goddamn thing for the public?
也是  也不是
Well, yes and no.
历史总是看上去比实际上要好
History has a way of looking better than it was.
或许莎士比亚是对的
Or perhaps Shakespeare was right.
我们都是疯子给瞎子带路
We're all just madmen leading the blind.
李女士  我是白宫的赛斯·格雷森
Ms. Lee. This is Seth Grayson, from the White House.
谢谢你接我的电话
Yeah, thank you for taking my call.
我就是有个问题
I just had a question.
有个记者
There, uh... there was a reporter.
等一下  我查查我的笔记
Give me a second. Let me just check my notes.
叫肖恩·杰弗瑞斯
Name's Sean Jeffries.
对  他在做一篇捐赠名单的报道
Yeah, he's working on a story about the donor list,
就是总统接受移植期间的事
around the time of the president's transplant.
不知你能不能来一趟
I was wondering if you could come in
我们好协调一下回应
and we can coordinate our response.
李女士  我们不希望大家认为
Ms. Lee, we don't want people to think
总统得到了特殊待遇
that the president got preferential treatment.
莉·哈维  无
凯·杜兰特  笔记本
马·厄舍  手机
莉·哈维  笔记本
天呐
Jesus.
你给了我什么啊  麦卡
What the hell did you give me, Mac?
天啊
Jesus.
你给了我什么啊  麦卡
What the hell did you give me, Mac?
我有关于头条网爆料来源的消息
I had a tip on where that Slugline story came from.
你该打给我的
You should have called me.
那也阻止不了什么
That wouldn't have stopped it.
-你是为这事而来吗  -不  我有别的消息
- Is that why you're here? - No, I got something else.
说吧
Tell me.
我想跟副总统聊聊
I'd like to talk to the vice president about it.
那不可能
That's not possible.
一切都要经过我
Everything goes through me.
我之前没机会解释清楚
Well, I didn't have a chance to explain myself.
太可惜了
That's too bad.
她什么样
What's she like?
她不忍受愚蠢  也不给人第二次机会
She doesn't suffer fools and she doesn't give second chances.
如果你不能让我再跟她见面
Well, if you can't get me in to talk to her again,
我会另想办法
I'll find some other way.
你冲昏头了
You're in over your head.
要么告诉我你知道什么  要么滚蛋
Tell me what you know or move along.
不
No.
我们没有  汉默施密特先生
We don't, Mr. Hammerschmidt.
不管你掌握了什么信息
Whatever information you have...
别再打给我了
Don't call me again.
我还担心我那天晚上说错话了
I was concerned I was out of line the other night.
或许吧
You might have been.
对不起  我有时候口不择言
I'm sorry. I don't even know what I'm saying sometimes.
算了
Forget it.
等一下
Hey, hang on a second.
我需要告诉你我的想法
I need to tell you how I'm feeling.
国家需要你  总统先生
The nation needs you, Mr. President.
-我们都需要你  -今天就到这儿吧
- We all need you. - We're done for today.
-不  -不
- No. - No?
不  你为什么不愿听我想说的话
No. Why don't you want to hear what I'm trying to tell you?
听着  你...够了
Listen. You... enough.
我爱你  你得知道
I love you. You need to know that.
-我只是想保护你  -你得冷静下来
- I'm only here to protect you. - You need to calm down.
你是怎么了  你为什么不愿听
What's wrong with you? Why don't you wanna hear
-我想说的话  -我没怎么
- what I'm telling you? - There is nothing wrong with me.
但你得回家了
But you need to go home.
是你找我的  是你叫我来的
You reached out to me. You brought me in. I...
够了
Enough.
-对不起  -他不在
- I'm sorry. - He's out.
我回头再来
I'll come back later.
不管是什么  我可以转交给他
Whatever it is, I can give it to him.
你可以托给我转交的  道格
You can trust me to hand it over, Doug.
-没叫你跟踪汤姆·耶茨啊  -有的
- You weren't directed to follow Tom Yates. - Yes, I was.
总统说要监视每个人
According to the president, everyone needs to be watched.
汤姆都不在这里了
Tom's not even here anymore.
弗兰西斯叫你跟踪他的吗
Francis asked you to follow him?
我担心一个人
I'm concerned about someone.
劳拉·莫雷蒂
Laura Moretti.
我知道她  和她丈夫的事
I know about her... and her husband.
你的行为是判断不佳的表现  道格
Your behavior shows poor judgment, Doug,
而且可能连累总统
and could be a liability for the president.
是  女士
Yes, ma'am.
等弗兰西斯回来把这给他
Give these to Francis when he gets back.
我可以给你拿到豁免权
I can get you immunity.
你只需要讲出真话
You just need to tell the truth.
确认沃克的证词都是真的
Confirm that all of Walker's testimony is true.
你不需要这么做
You don't have to do it.
不  莫琳  我要公开说
No, Maureen, I want this on the record.
你怎么能这么背叛安德伍德夫妇
How dare you betray the Underwoods like this?
我们说完了  议员
We're done here, Congressman.
谢谢你抽时间
Well, thank you for your time.
请你准备好
So you're prepared,
司法委员会很快会签发传票
a subpoena will be coming soon from the Judiciary Committee.
国务卿女士
Madam Secretary.
好
你想进去吗
Do you wanna come in?
是我导致了你丈夫的死
I'm the reason your husband's dead.
我逼迫卫生和人类服务部部长
I forced the Secretary of Health and Human Services...
把弗兰西斯·安德伍德插在捐赠名单上他之前
to put Francis Underwood in front of him on the donor list.
如果你觉得我是禽兽我也能理解
I understand if you think I'm a monster.
但我不后悔
But I'd do it again.
为了救总统  我愿不惜一切
To save the president, I'd do anything.
你真觉得我不知道吗  道格
You really think that I didn't know, Doug?
是时机暴露了
The timing gave it away.
来吧  快进屋
Come on. Come on in.
你以为是怎么回事
What did you think was going on here?
我操你不是因为我喜欢你
I'm not fucking you because I like you.
我操你是因为我恨你
I'm fucking you because I hate you.
出去
Get out.
滚出我的车
Get out of my car.
快滚出我的车
Get the fuck out of my car.
滚
Get out!
麦卡伦给了你什么
What did Macallan give you?
-我不知道你在说什么  -我听见你说话了
- I don't know what you're talking about. - I heard you.
他给了你什么东西
You got something from him.
什么叫"你听见我说话了"
What do you mean you heard me?
你还在监视我吗
Were you watching me, too?
他是你什么人
Who was he to you?
喝一杯吗
Want a drink?
我不喝酒
I don't drink.
对了
Oh, right.
我和他睡过
I was with him.
我还年轻  不该跟他睡的时候
When I was young and shouldn't have been with him.
你喜欢什么  道格
What gets you off, Doug?
有吗
Anything?
要是麦卡伦给了你什么  我们应该上交
If Macallan gave you something, we should hand it over.
你喜欢吗
Did you like it?
什么
What?
监视我
Watching me.
喜欢
Yes.
你喜欢你看见的吗
You liked what you saw?
这是你来找我的原因吗
That why you came here?
那好吧
Well, then.
我要去健身房  跑步消解压力
Going to the gym. Run off some of this stress.
你的教练呢
Where's your trainer?
他有一段时间都不会来了
Oh, he won't be coming around for a while.
他有个表情我可不会怀念
He did have a facial expression I won't miss.
是吗
Is that so?
那种凝固的笑  很瘆人
Sort of perma-smile. It was creepy.
也许他只是开心罢了
Maybe he's just happy.
我不担心开心
Happiness isn't my concern.
现在不  从来都不
Not now, not ever.
这局面太不幸了  克莱尔
It's a tragic situation, Claire.
-我知道  -我可以给你看看正在发生的事
- I know. - I could show you what's happening.
我看过照片了
I've seen the images.
务必要让民众知道霍姆斯城正在发生什么
It's important people know what's going on in Homs.
你改主意了吗
Are you having second thoughts?
只是现在时机还不到
It's just the timing isn't right yet.
因为你丈夫得不到支持
Because your husband doesn't have the support.
我们得有理有据
We need to make a case.
你做声明之前  让全世界做好准备
Prepare the world for when you make a statement.
我认为弗兰西斯得来做主导
I think Francis needs to be front and center on this.
你没查到麦卡伦告诉佩特罗夫什么了
You never found out what Macallan told Petrov?
我的线人说  他没说什么真正有用的
My sources say he never gave him anything concrete.
-他给了莉安一些东西  -我们希望如此
- Well, he gave LeAnn something. - Well, that was our hope.
也许是时候再把她请回来了
Maybe it's time to invite her back in.
也许吧  我得上楼了
Maybe. I need to get back upstairs.
下次在我办公室见
The next time we meet will be in my office.
我不觉得你丈夫该做主导
I... I don't think your husband should be front and center.
应该是你
I think it should be you.
我没问你的意见
I didn't ask you what you think.
你得有所准备  克莱尔
You need to be armed, Claire.
无论他怎样
It's important that you can walk away
你务必得能全身而退
from anything that happens to him.
去他们的
They can kiss my ass.
参议员韦斯特维尔特有意要我
I got an offer from Senator Westervelt.
我也在找
I'm looking, too.
但想下这艘船越来越困难了
But it's getting harder and harder to get off this ship.
我妻子在哪
Where is my wife?
她去哪了
Where has she gone?
如果她是你妻子  你不会想知道吗
If she was your wife, wouldn't you wonder?
好  安德伍德夫人
Yes, Mrs. Underwood.
别担心  这事没发生过
Don't worry. This never happened.
不用你告诉我
You don't have to tell me.
-道格  -该死
- Doug. - Shit.
我该过去吗
Should I come in?
不  除非你把你手里的东西给我
No. Not until you give me what you've got.
总统先生
Mr. President.
"一位白宫内部人士透露
"A source deep within the White House...
安德伍德总统确实
confirms President Underwood
曾利用可疑情报
used questionable intelligence
为关闭投票中心找理由
to justify voting center closures,
从而使选举陷入了混乱"
which threw the election into chaos."
你觉得会是谁
Who do you think it is?
可能是格林
Green, probably.
-我们高估了他的忠诚  -我明白了
- We overestimated his loyalty. - I see.
要不
I mean...
还能是谁
who else could it be?
我能做些什么
How can I help?
我们得自救
We need to save ourselves here.
-这事对我俩都很不利  凯茜  -我明白
- It's as much your head as mine, Cathy. - I understand.
我需要你编写额外的材料
I need you to create additional documents
为追捕卡拉比找理由
that justify going after Kalabi.
制造书面痕迹来支撑我们
A paper trail that will support our actions
选举日在田纳西采取的行动
that we took on Election Day in Tennessee.
我不确定
I'm not sure...
该是什么样的材料
what those documents would be.
可你够聪明  对吧  凯茜
Well, but you're smart, Cathy, aren't you?
你会想到的
I mean, you can figure it out.
让我看看你有多聪明吧
Why don't you just show me how smart you are.
-当然  总统先生  -还有在联合国的演讲
- Of course, Mr. President. - And the presentation at the UN.
-关于叙利亚的  -必须进行
- With Syria? - It needs to happen.
-好吧  -可能会引起非议
- Very well. - There's a possibility of talks,
但我们得让所有相关方重新回到谈判桌上
but we need to get all the interested parties back to the table.
当然
Of course.
你是个好外交官  凯茜
You're a good diplomat, Cathy.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
另外  克莱尔呢
And where is Claire?
她现在需要保持些距离
She needed a little distance right now.
直到我们看清我到底怎么回事
Till we find out what's happening with me.
所以我现在必须指望你了  凯茜
That's why I need to rely on you, Cathy. Now.
很高兴你这么想  弗兰西斯
Well, I'm glad you feel that way, Francis.
是我  我可以见面了
Yes. I'm ready to meet.
我现在就要见面  马上
I wanna meet now. Right now.
在一次
After a tumultuous election,
前所未有的混乱选举后
the likes of which have never been seen,
美国面临着更多的问题
America faces more questions...
我现在一堆破事  没时间应付你
Shit is insane right now. I don't have any more time for you.
如果最近从白宫泄露出来的情报
If the recent leaks coming out of the White House
得到证实  总统将面临...
prove to be true, the president could face...
白宫身份牌  你从哪弄的
A White House ID? Where did you get that?
我还以为是你给的
I thought this came from you.
你说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
-我现在是副新闻发言人了  -去你妈的
- I'm deputy press secretary. - The fuck you are.
我接到了副总统办公室的电话
I got a call from the vice president's office,
让我过来
asking me to come in.
我到的时候  这个已经准备好了
And when I got here, this was waiting for me.
我刚才一小时都在办手续
I just spent the last hour doing my paperwork.
我没时间跟你胡扯
I don't have time for this.
加勒特·沃克总统的爆炸性证词
President Garrett Walker's bombshell testimony, which...
我有国务卿杜兰特的辞职信
I have Secretary Durant's resignation.
我相信她就是泄密者
I believe she was the leak,
并且可能要为
and might have to take responsibility
选举当晚发生的事负责
for whatever happened on election night.
先生  司法委员会现在随时
Sir, the judiciary could issue a resolution
会发出弹劾决议了
for impeachment any day now.
我们得现实地面对这事对总统的伤害
We need to be realistic about damage to the president
即便参议院不定罪
even if the Senate doesn't convict.
你承诺的是党内警告
You promised us censure.
杜兰特的泄密已经起到同样的效果了  不是吗
Well, Durant's leak took care of that, didn't it?
我们有个应对参议院的计划
So, we have a plan for the Senate.
我建议重点保护副总统
I suggest we work on protecting the vice president.
确保她在整个过程中能全身而退
Make sure she exits this whole process unscathed.
我们要怎么才能做到
And how do we do that?
声称不知情  副总统没审阅任何相关信息
Plead ignorance. The vice president wasn't read into anything.
什么也不知道
Didn't know anything.
-也什么都没做  -不行的
- Didn't do anything. - That won't play.
她会看上去不知情  但人们知道并非如此
She'll look uninformed, and the people know she isn't.
距离会让她看起来无辜
Oh, the distance will help her look innocent.
无辜或有罪  有能力或没用  不管怎样
Innocent, guilty, capable, incompetent, whatever it is...
公众都会往反方向想
the public is going to think the opposite.
所以真是怎么都输
So, really there is no winning.
照你的意思来吧
Whatever you think is best.
如果我被判无罪  你会有四年时间
You're gonna have four years to prove yourself
在位子上证明自己  希望是八年
on the inside if I'm acquitted. Hopefully, eight.
但如果我被判有罪呢
But what happens if I'm not acquitted?
我们现在不用考虑那个
We don't have to deal with that right now.
不  我想听到一个计划
No, I want to hear a plan.
这正是找你来的原因
That's why you're here.
给我冷冰冰  硬梆梆的事实
To give me the cold, hard facts.
我的盘算不比您高明  总统先生
Oh, your calculus is as good as mine, Mr. President.
根本没有计划
There is no plan.
只能拖住司法委员会  稳住参议院
Except slow down judiciary, secure the Senate.
我担心一个人
I'm concerned about someone.
劳拉·莫雷蒂
Laura Moretti.
为什么把这个也放进来
Why did you include this?
你跟克莱尔谈这个什么劳拉·莫雷蒂
You and Claire talking about a Laura Moretti?
我想让你知道  先生  她知道了
I wanted you to know, sir, that she knows.
我在名单上帮你插了队
I jumped you on the list.
好获得肝脏捐赠
To receive a donor liver.
我强迫卫生和人类服务部部长调高了你的排名
I forced the HHS Secretary to move you up.
-那不可能  -我威胁了她  先生
- That's not possible. - I threatened her, sir.
这是前所未有的道德违规  但我不后悔这样做
It was an unprecedented ethical violation. But I don't regret it.
我独守这个秘密  好让你...
I kept it to myself, so that you would...
在有人发现时可以合理推诿
have plausible deniability if anyone found out.
我也没告诉安德伍德夫人
I didn't tell Mrs. Underwood either.
她是从别处知道的
She learned another way.
她知道却没告诉我
She knew and didn't tell me.
看起来是这样
Seems so.
她对耶茨的监控反应如何
And how did she react to the Yates surveillance?
那个她怎么说的
What did she say about that?
她没对我表达她的感受  先生
She didn't show her feelings to me, sir.
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
我与你同在  先生
I'm here for you, sir.
直到永远
Always.
你对安德伍德夫人有疑虑吗
Do you have concerns about Mrs. Underwood?
-你有吗  -我永远不会这样讲
- Do you? - I would never say that.
我要给你看点东西
I want to show you something.
有45分钟我不清楚她的行踪
There's 45 minutes where I can't account for her whereabouts.
我不知道她去了哪里  见了什么人
I don't know where she went or who she saw.
但是她对我说谎了
But she lied to me.
我认为你应该休息一下  先生
I, uh... I think you should get some rest, sir.
总统没有让我审阅
The president didn't read me in.
我不在房间里
I wasn't in the room.
总统没有让我审阅
The president didn't read me in.
我不在房间里
I wasn't in the room.
我对此毫不知情
I didn't know anything about it.
总统没有让我审阅
The president didn't read me in.
我不在房间里
I wasn't in the room.
我对此毫不知情
I didn't know anything about it.
怎么样  弗兰西斯
How's that, Francis?
最新消息  国务卿凯瑟琳·杜兰特
This is just in. Secretary of State Catherine Durant
将在众议院司法委员会作证
to appear in front of the House Judiciary Committee.
这个意外令已经非常戏剧化的...
This comes as yet another surprise in the already dramatic...
-什么时候收到的  -不久之前
- When did it come in? - A short while ago.
不是凯茜·杜兰特
It's not Cathy Durant.
我们能确定吗
Are we sure?
她争取了豁免权
She negotiated immunity.
她作证时
And she's going on record
将公开她知道的一切
with everything she knows when she testifies.
我们知道是谁吗
Do we have any idea?
不知道
No.
好
Good.
谢谢
Thanks.
又过生日
活着比死了强
生日快乐
特朗普上任后一直麻烦不断  不仅一系列政策遭到媒体的广泛批评
还有多个国会委员会在对俄罗斯干扰2016大选进行调查
在前联调局局长科米被突然撤职后  媒体普遍认为特朗普干预司法
许多媒体开始讨论是否应该弹劾他  但也有冷静的声音指出
目前特朗普所属的共和党在参众两院都占多数  弹劾基本无可能
当年比尔·克林顿因为在莱温斯基事件上公然说谎  国会启动弹劾程序
众议院投票表决同意弹劾后  弹劾的决议在参议院没有获得足够票数
在参众两院的两次投票中  克林顿所属的民主党党员大都坚定地站在总统这边
目前批评特朗普的声浪虽高  但都是来自民主党
而即便在特朗普的一些言行明显离谱  甚至有违法嫌疑的情况下
国会共和党也不敢对他有太多微辞  所以媒体才认为目前弹劾可能性很小
可以看出  涉及到弹劾时  美国两党议员
基本都是根据自己的党派归属来决定立场的